

Jelena Grigorjeva

Profile

Highly experienced, creative and self-motivated Sales Manager professional with over 10 years extensive experience in the Luxury Retail Sector.

Based in Dubai with exceptional customer service and best practices knowledge developed from Top Brands in the UK, Europe and Middle East available immediately.

Dubai, UAE +971 526212369

jelenauk@hotmail.co.uk

Professional Experience

ETSHTOO - A&H Al Ghurair Investment - Dubai, UAE October 2019 - Present

Operation Store Manager for Twinset brand in Dubai Marina Mall and Dubai Mall with 5 - 7 employees.

Job responsibilities:

- Driving and supporting the team in achieving the monthly and yearly targets, liaising with staff members to ensure they are up to date with all relevant individual and store KPIs.
- Daily and monthly detailed reports about business progress and development, insight feedback.
- Focused on all operational aspects and ensuring all company requirements are met to the highest standards.
- Handling of all internal and independent collaborations, liaising with local Mall managers and police to obtain permits for contractors and subsequently supervise all procedures taking place
- Holds regular staff trainings to permanent staff and inductions to new joiners.
- Daily operations management, till reconciliation and cash deposits.

<u>Achievement:</u> increased the sales for 20-30% for every month. Reduce 90% of the damages in the store. Developed and successfully implemented "no 0 sales" program. Promoted 3 members of stuff based on each talents and skills.

KRISTINA FIDELSKAYA - Dubai, UAE

2016 - 2018

Boutique Manager in luxury fashion sector. Successfully opened a new store, recruited and built a high performing sales team.

Job responsibilities:

- •Full-time Manager tasked with facilitating daily shift operations.
- Providing an exceptional customer service to VIP clientele.
- •Ensure that sales targets are achieved and, where possible, exceeded.
- Merchandise and conducted regular inventories of stock to optimize supply levels.
- Addressed and resolved escalating customer service issues.
- •Provided formal and one-on-one training to new sales associates.
- Visual Merchandising.
- Participating at various exclusive fashion events.

<u>Achievement:</u> developed and implemented client service program, which expanded client base by 35%.

Professional Strengths

- Excellent customer service
- Luxury attitude
- Team builder
- Ability to motivate, cultivate and develop sales team
- Details oriented
- Excellent negotiation skills

Key Strengths

- Strong Luxury Brands Background
- Result oriented
- Middle East Retail Trends
- Multi-tasking
- Customer focused
- Effective Communicate & Presentation
- Positive attitude
- Organizational skills

IT Skills

 Expert in all Office: Word, Excel (generating formulas and schemes) PowerPoint, Outlook, POS, Oracle, Ai, Ps

Languages

- English
- Russian
- Latvian
- Arabic (basic)

AL TAYER GROUP - Dubai, UAE

2015 - 2016

Team Leader (Brands: Jimmy Choo, Balenciaga, DVF and Harvey Nichols). With strong enthusiasm and desire for fashion brands was leading the team of 4 people.

Job Responsibilities:

- •Provide support to the Store Manager in order to manage and deliver KPI performance for the individual stores within Al Tayer Group.
- Maintaining excellent level of product knowledge, following up on market trends and monitoring competitor activity.
- Maintaining high standards of visual merchandising and stock keeping.
- •Building and cultivating strong customer relationships through excellent personal presentation, outstanding customer service, assisting clients in exceeding their expectations and consistent follow up at all times.

Achievement: performed excellent selling skills and inspired others.

MICHAEL KORS - London, UK

2012 - 2014 - Supervisor

TATEOSSIAN JEWELLERY - London, UK

2010 - 2012 - Senior Sales Associate

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration with specialization in Company Management, Baltic International Academy - Riga, Latvia

Completion: 2006 - 2009

References

Available upon request